how's it going everyone cameras only
father with a very special video today
so people have been sending me message
after message saying came with five go
look at the new Sonic voices custom
heels trailer like what the [ __ ] is that
[ __ ] Sonic force is that what I mean
I stopped watch it I stopped falling you
got it be to God I said I stopped
following Sonic the Hedgehog 15 years
ago some [ __ ] I mean the last thing I
remember healing about was a Sonic boom
which came out like 2010 and I haven't
heard anything about that like since I
mean go off the face of the earth I'm
alive I mean boom I mean it went boom
like you know our Sonic boom because it
looked like a piece of [ __ ] like I'm
also beating out two in the bottom right
now picking [ __ ] I probably am you know
no [ __ ] anyway this kid let's tell
really sucks [ __ ] damn most million
views look at all of this like that boom
I'm just liking that [ __ ] I mean
put the [ __ ] trying to fool I mean ma
go to Google top and science was cussing
heels trailer sorry for the cut else in
here trailer click on the video
no no one before a [ __ ] the one below
it click on that [ __ ] dislike it yeah
dislike that [ __ ] come on no the one
blower mama don't go all day come on
no look that one click of a [ __ ] this
lawyer is it are you stupid I don't care
just go do it
are you serious mom you really gonna say
it to me me I'm cable one thing for five
he'll talk to me are heavy
oh you revolve yeah this mommy he can
fall [ __ ] mouth he's got money
I oh my God you're stupid you're stupid
he'd be your [ __ ] ass oh my God
I'll believe in the babies [ __ ] I'll be
will slap your [ __ ] ass woman come on
up on down right now
oh my God no stupid [ __ ] oh my God
mama I'm filming this [ __ ]
they know you're being stupid come on oh
my God mama you're on YouTube being so
stupid I got mom Mike you can channel it
you're on right now
you guys know Oh No
yeah no no no drama I'm watching a video
mama
shut the [ __ ] up okay two minutes that's
how long the video is two minutes that's
all I think about the DUI I'm here [ __ ]
I'm kill only five sorry about the guys
stupid people being stupid stupid boom
come on I don't got all day
oh God la look at look at that look at
that [ __ ] I mean God loved her right
at the beginning gotta have a classic
five rock that that's the piece of them
sorry that's onyx pixel from Sonic
Underground
look at that oh my God I mean damn so I
want to take you take a dump in here
[ __ ] [ __ ] that's a better badder chairs
they're already [ __ ] that that picture
class not school though what that's cuz
you know they start at the sock on [ __ ]
is this year like super over a wall
falls and [ __ ] cause of my butt
oh no cuz this is a custom it's a cousin
character I think there's only one thing
I can do but I'm done I'm done walking
this year this is here I'm also I must
be sitting on the toilet right now I
mean [ __ ] what can I do now do look at
do I was in Tehran all right flush it
down the toilet [ __ ]